Hello. I'm Halie Koehler, a UI/UX Designer, Front-end Developer and Visual Artist.

(210) 232-0196 halie@halie.online www.halie.online linkedin.com/in/haliekoehler/ github.com/haliekoehler

Combining extensive artistic experience and skill, with 3+ years of hands on web development, creates a highly unique skillset with a wide range of capablities.

SKILLS

Software

Adobe XD / Illustrator / Photoshop / InDesign / Dimensions / Animate, Atom, WebStorm

Programming

HTML5, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Bulma, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Git, Hugo, Vue.js

Personal

Art & Design, Self Management, Creativity, Attention to Detail, Emotional Intelligence

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Codeup, San Antonio, TX

Oct. 2016 - Feb. 2017

Fine Art & Illustration

RMCAD, Denver, CO

Aug. 2008 - Dec. 2011

Visual Arts

NESA, San Antonio, TX

Graduated 2008

REFERENCES

Available upon request

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Desginer & Developer CyberFortress, San Antonio, TX

- Established company's brand and aesthetics.
- Designed mockups based on insurance regulations for investor review.
- Built out and managed front-end code for company website and application.
- Created unique vector graphics and illustrations for web and other various media.

Software Developer

Allcat Claims Service - Boerne, TX

- Met with clients to establish guidelines and requirements for multiple websites and complex applications.
- Designed mockups for client review and developer reference.
- Developed and maintained all front-end code for multiple websites and applications.

Owner / Freelance Artist

H.Koehler Artwork - Colorado & Texas

- Managed freelance art career as legitimized business
- Selectively accepted commissions and established contracts specific to client and job.

Resident Artist

Emerald City Organics, Boulder, CO

- Painted large scale murals for mulitple dispensaries throughout Colorado.
- Managed, designed and submitted ads for multiple publications on a monthly basis.
- Established and maintained company's overall aesthetic
- Designed logos, business cards, signage, etc. for all dispensaries.
- Directed paint crews in prepartion for new stores.

- 2019 -

06 / 2017 - 10 / 2018

02 / 2012 - 11 / 2013